all right well they really have a lot of
cones out here okay so here's the
joystick alright guys so I'm sitting in
the backseat of trees here um this is
some people have nightmares about this
okay you have a way to push the prank
good Hey but it's not engaged I can't I
can't break okay okay use on expressway
only good we're only on the expressway
okay yes all right so no look at the
driver oh look he's gonna turn wait
I guess one oh no I turned it off no oh
I forgot to twist this to you okay there
we go all right let's go
oh yeah who wants to buy a comma
drive-by-wire prius $50,000 we will sell
you a drive-by-wire prius you can have a
prius just like this one where you can
turn the wheel huge amounts huge make
tight prius turns never get locked out
what else can we do in the advertisement
for these self-driving prius business
driving itself guys look at China itself
I'm done with a combination of software
mods and a few extra pandas and by a few
I mean one we use the extra panda oh
yeah look at that acceleration free is
acceleration
we're not gonna go faster than that yeah
well and you're so limited by what the
cool
yeah it's dragging a car the joysticks
kind of hard but um so you guys could
see I can turn it this way we all goes
like that oh you
that's rate limit oh that's that's with
a rate limit you guys yeah yeah oh wait
oh wait guys we gotta strap in hang on
push forward to go forward there you go
okay twist the joist up can its ultra
everything you know it is the ER guys
it's the EON doing this oh my god gentle
gentle gentle reduce jerk oh yeah
so this is this is why we came out to
the to the airfield today so we could
test our drive-by-wire Prius
acceleration isn't limited but break is
that seems weird this is a toy guys this
is the favorite vehicle
Yolo live demo what do you mean a Yolo
live demo this is a live demo we're
rolling
that's what he's saying she hook it up
to an Xbox controller what you don't
like our top con Joyce deck you turn it
on the car is slowly moving car oh my
god can you control them outside the car
we're not gonna control it from outside
the car we did this once before yeah I
read up one of the Kama panel plans I
don't know if anyone's reporting Mazda
that's the bad question Bob wait we were
moving the weight limit yes okay guys
like you should see this wheel can
really whip wet
where is Florida it's like over there
maybe why did it take off myself
that's it creep Oh why'd it take off by
itself because it just creeped it did
the system disengage
yeah hey back on
no doesn't like it doesn't like it
there's a Fault in the excel wait turn
engage okay we're good up sorry I think
it's because all my okay that faltered
out Oh
if faults when he goes too fast it's
probably went too far with the rate but
the right I don't know let's just leave
very little bit on there's nothing we
can't do with that other rate limit I
mean I can do five instead of three
click twice
should I wait you turn off now I'll turn
off the steering yeah hey so now cruise
controls turned off
I'd only hit those things what are those
things
sorry that's pretty good
oh yeah this is the model with the Park
Assist that's called Park assess its
assisting us with parking Oh see that
time it did it you feel like stayed on
the brakes a little things lots of Drive
is that not an iPad pro or what now this
is a touchscreen so the problem is what
happens in ESP kicks in oh it actually
kicks you out yeah what don't I use peel
[Music]
wait IPA and Toyota isn't that good well
hacked IPA is that good no what we
didn't buy the car for this test this is
just calming eyes Prius
how do you break with the joystick
pullback doesn't let you turn on with
the SPF okay I mean that's sensible
well that steering really doesn't kick
you out yeah I mean we can use another
f7d panda and tell it that it's never
ESPE yes and the go system doesn't know
I guess I mean okay you know what there
has to be another interface that it's
using for a EB you know yeah maybe we
just need to find it yeah but those
usually have like low-level limitations
like much on deceleration speed yeah
probably
really high because it's a B what do you
mean 1480 you can do oh so 25 miles per
hour deceleration it's max Delta and
then what happens and it kicks you out
did I stop stop breaking oh you a BB at
more than 40 you create accidents the
Delta speed the due to a V is more than
40 kph yeah but it doesn't know like the
braking controller doesn't know that
what when you send the packet to the
braking control I'm sure there's just
some packet we can find that we can send
it as braking control it'll just trigger
the brakes oh yeah yeah yeah maybe we
can look for
yes yeah so we have no we have no track
to track she chose turned off her house
we don't have a longitudinal control on
the car we only have lateral control the
Carters trying to make the car stop it's
not stopping that's easy to turn on and
off yeah now we can go we will we will
drag race the cars later guys all right
right shall we drive back to the Ford
yeah so we're gonna be testing some
autonomous stuff we're gonna see if it
can look at a role in going way faster
to roll it
well don't hit the floor without a
tragedy if you just read you get the
steering control we golf into those
grasses over there
all right scope ease thanks for joining
into this fully self-driving Prius on a
closed test course bye-bye
yeah it's a joystick if you didn't see
the joystick there's the Dresden tape
the phone to the driver's seat we got
any on up there the Aeons actually this
is your the Panda on the enemy of the
Panda on the car why not use controller
guys it doesn't matter what joystick you
use what's the purpose of this we're
showing off our fully drive-by-wire tree
and your prius can be fully
drive-by-wire or two for only $50,000 oh
you know I got a call from Davis feeder
right yeah yeah very you know I'm just
saying our competitors charge more than
double what we are charging you come to
me $50,000 and you bring me Prius and
we'll make that Prius drive like this